<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home Pages on Walla Walla County Amateur Radio Emergency Service | W7DP Club</title>
    <link>https://wwares.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home Pages on Walla Walla County Amateur Radio Emergency Service | W7DP Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wwares.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Net Control Resources</title>
      <link>https://wwares.github.io/net-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wwares.github.io/net-control/</guid>
      <description>Net Control Schedule 1 Jan - 1 Feb 2022 (pdf)Download
Tuesday Net Control Script 3-3-22 (pdf)Download
Thursday Net Control Script 3-3-22 (pdf)Download
Net CheckIn Log 3-3-22 (pdf)Download
EOC IC-205 Frequency Plan May 2021 (pdf)Download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Images</title>
      <link>https://wwares.github.io/resources/nasa-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wwares.github.io/resources/nasa-images/</guid>
      <description>The below images are from the NASA Image and Video Library &amp;ndash; indulge yourself, revel in their beauty. Also, the built-in figure shortcode is shown for each image.
 {{&amp;lt; figure img=&amp;#34;sun.jpg&amp;#34; caption=&amp;#34;The Sun is the star at the center of the Solar System. It is a nearly perfect sphere of hot plasma, with internal convective motion that generates a magnetic field via a dynamo process. It is by far the most important source of energy for life on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://wwares.github.io/resources/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wwares.github.io/resources/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://wwares.github.io/resources/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wwares.github.io/resources/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://wwares.github.io/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wwares.github.io/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Event Schedule    DATE EVENT     4 Dec 2021 Parade of Lights   21 May 2022 Onion Man Triathlon   3 - 5 Jun 2022 Tour of Walla Walla Bicycle Race    Meetings Schedule    DATE / TIME MEETING     1st Tuesday of the Month at 7pm W7DP Club Meeting   3rd Monday of the Month at 7pm ARES Meeting    *There are no meetings in December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>W7DP Walla Walla Valley Amateur Radio Club</title>
      <link>https://wwares.github.io/w7dp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wwares.github.io/w7dp/</guid>
      <description>Monthly Meeting Meetings are held the 1st Tuesday of each month at 7pm.
The W7DP clubhouse is at the corner of SE Justice Ave and Taumarson Rd, College Place, WA.
Club Officers  Timber Burton N7DJE - President Davena Burton KC7USG - Vice-president Mikel Potts KB7POT - Secretary Keith Carlin N7ACW - Treasurer Don Grenseman W7UB - Registered Agent David Malcolm KC7JIX - W7DP Station Trustee  Email: w7dp@wwares.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WA7WWC, Lewis Peak Amateur Repeater Association</title>
      <link>https://wwares.github.io/lewispeak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wwares.github.io/lewispeak/</guid>
      <description>Repeaters to serve amateur radio communications in Walla Walla County Repeater frequencies:  146.960 MHz (-600 kHz) (PL 74.4) 443.450 MHz (+5 MHz) (PL 123.0)  Packet Nodes:  AL1Q-7 (W2W) on 145.070 MHz, 1200 baud AL1Q-9 (W2W2) on 145.530 MHz, 1200 baud  Board of Directors  President - Jeff Stidham AL1Q Vice-president - Mikel Potts KB7POT Secretary/Treasurer - Davena Burton KT7JE Emergency Coordinator - Keith Carlin N7ACW Registered Agent - Rick Guse KI7GBU WA7WWC Trustee - Jeff Stidham AL1Q  Purpose Provide voice and digital communication on VHF/UHF for emergency support of Walla Walla County Office of Emergency Management Support Walla Walla County Amateur Radio Emergency Service</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
